A Guide to the Papers of Harry Edward Neal, 1910 (1945-1975) 1993
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Harry Edward Neal, 1910 (1945-1974) 1974
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
8915-k
This collection consists of ca. 250 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content Information
The collection contains photographs for Communication - From Stone Age to Space Age, a typescript of Nature's Guardians: Your Career in Conservation; research material for The Secret Service in Action and The Story of the Secret Service; research material, typescripts, correspondence, and photographs for "The Story of Whaling"; and research material, photographs, correspondence, typescript, proof and book reviews for The United States Secret Service.
Contents List
- Communication - From Stone Age to Space Age Photographs 1974, b/w photos (Box 1)
- Nature's Guardians: Your Career in Conservation ca. 1956, TMs, carbon (Box 1)
- The Secret Service in Action& n.d. Research Material 1949-1970, 2 folders (Box 1)
- The Story of the Secret Service Research Material 1965-1971, 2 folders (Box 1)
- The Story of the Secret Service Research Material n.d., 2 folders (Box 2)
- "The Story of Whaling" 1953-1955, TMs (Box 2)
- "The Story of Whaling" n.d., TMs (Box 2)
- "The Story of Whaling" - Third Version 1955 Apr, TMs (Box 2)
- "The Story of Whaling" - Third Version, w/ letter 1955 & 1958, TMs (Box 2)
- "The Story of Whaling" Correspondence 1951-1955 (Box 3)
- "The Story of Whaling" Photographs 1950, B/w photos (Box 3)
- "The Story of Whaling" Printed Material 1945-1955, 2 folders (Box 3)
- "The Story of Whaling" Printed Research Material ca.1951-1958 (Box 3)
- "The Story of Whaling" Research Notes 1947-1954 (Box 3)
- "Tales About Whales" ["The Story of Whaling"] Research Notes 1951 (Box 3)
- The United States Secret Service, Chapters 2-20 ca. 1960, TMs, 2 folders (Box 4)
- The United States Secret Service 1960, Galley Proof (Box 4)
- The United States Secret Service, w/ corrections 1960, Galley Proof (Box 4)
- The United States Secret Service Correspondence 1959 (Box 4)
- The United States Secret Service Correspondence 1960-1962, 2 folders (Box 5)
- The United States Secret Service Book Reviews & Printed Material 1960-1961 (Box 5)
- Newspaper Articles in the Boston Globe and The New York Mirror re The United States Secret Service by Harry E. Neal & Walter S. Bowen 1960 (Box 5)
- The United States Secret Service Photographs n.d., B/w photos (Box 5)
- Publicity Photographs for The United States Secret Service, w/ accompanying correspondence 1960, B/w photos (Box 5)
- The United States Secret Service Research Notes 1910, & 1929-1970 (Box 5)
- Unidentified microfilm w/ prints n.d. (Box 5)
- Obituary and biographical information about Harry E. Neal 1975, 1993, n.d. (Box 5)